Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - J
        - J-A Groove - Release the tension, 1986; SR-16035; J-A Groove (Box 303)
          Catalog # STU-711; A-side Matrix # STU-711A
          Studio Records
          Oxon Hill, Maryland
        - J. B. Allstars - I like it like that, 1989; SR-16036; J. B. Allstars (Box 303)
          Catalog # HNT 1001; A-side Matrix # HNT-1001-1A
          Hi Note
          United Kingdom
        - J-Bone - Same to me, 2001; SR-16037; J-Bone (Box 303)
          Catalog # 0-54435; A-side Matrix # 0-54435A
          212 Records
          New York, New York
        - J. Geils Band - Bloodshot, 1973; SR-16038; J. Geils Band (Box 303)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # SD 7260; A-side Matrix # ST-A 732801-1D
          Atlantic
        - J. Geils Band - Bloodshot, 1973; SR-16039; J. Geils Band (Box 303)
          Catalog # SD 7260; A-side Matrix # ST-A-732801-1C-2HD
          Canada
        - J. Geils Band - Sanctuary., 1978; SR-16040; J. Geils Band (Box 303)
          Catalog # SO-17006; A-side Matrix # SO-1-17006
          EMI America
          Hollywood, California
        - J-Kwon - Tipsy, 2003; SR-16041; J-Kwon (Box 303)
          Catalog # 82876-58460-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-57597-1SA-RE1
          So So Def
        - J-Kwon - Tipsy, 2003; SR-16042; J-Kwon (Box 303)
        - J. Little - The hump is on, 1994; SR-16043; J. Little (Box 303)
          Catalog # DMD 2158; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-73566-73557-73570-1
        - J-Live - Longevity; Braggin' writes, 1995; SR-16044; J-Live (Box 303)
          Catalog # RSP 001; A-side Matrix # RSP-001-A
          Raw Shack Productions
          Brooklyn, New York
        - J-Live - Can I get it?; Hush the crowd, 1996; SR-16045; J-Live (Box 303)
          Catalog # RSP002V; A-side Matrix # RSP-002V-A
        - J-Live - Can I get it?; Hush the crowd, 1996; SR-16046; J-Live (Box 303)
        - J-Shin - One night stand; Whatever u want, 1999; SR-16047; J-Shin (Box 303)
          Catalog # DMD 2530; A-side Matrix # STDM-2530A-1
        - J'son - I should cheat on you, 1998; SR-16048; J'son (Box 303)
          Catalog # ED-10819; A-side Matrix # ED-10891-1
          Hollywood Records
          Burbank, California
        - Ja Rule - Exodus (Disc one), 2005; SR-16049; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16050. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005813-01 LP01; A-side Matrix # B0005813-01-LP1A
          The Inc Records
        - Ja Rule - Exodus (Disc two), 2005; SR-16050; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16049. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005813-01 LP02; A-side Matrix # B0005813-01-LP2A
        - Ja Rule - I cry, 2001; SR-16051; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 15286-1; A-side Matrix # 314-572-856-1A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Ja Rule - New York, 2004; SR-16052; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 16222-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 16222-1A
        - Ja Rule - Caught up, 2004; SR-16053; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 16243-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16149-1B
        - Ja Rule - Exodus (Disc one), 2005; SR-16054; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16055. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16459-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16459-1/DEFF-16460-1A
        - Ja Rule - Exodus (Disc two), 2005; SR-16055; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16054. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16461-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16459-1/DEFF-16461-1A
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Disc one), 2001; SR-16056; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16057. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 586 437-1; A-side Matrix # 314-586-438-1-A
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Disc two), 2001; SR-16057; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16056. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 586 439-1; A-side Matrix # 314-586-439-1-A
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Disc one), 2001; SR-16058; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16059. Double album.
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Disc two), 2001; SR-16059; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16058. Double album.
        - Ja Rule - Wonderful, 2004; SR-16060; Ja Rule; Ashanti; R. Kelly (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 16149-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 16149-1A
        - Ja Rule - Caught up, 2004; SR-16061; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 16254-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16149-1B
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc one), 2001; SR-16062; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16063. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF15414-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15414-1A
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc two), 2001; SR-16063; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16062. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF15415-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15415-1C
        - Ja Rule - Exodus (Intro); Me, 2005; SR-16064; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 16458-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16458-1A
        - Ja Rule - R.U.L.E. (Disc one), 2004; SR-16065; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16066. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002955-01; A-side Matrix # B0002955-01A
        - Ja Rule - R.U.L.E. (Disc two), 2004; SR-16066; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16065. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002955-01; A-side Matrix # B0002955-01C
        - Ja Rule - The last temptation (Disc one), 2002; SR-16067; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16068. Double album.
          Catalog # 440 063 487-1; A-side Matrix # 440-063-488-1A
        - Ja Rule - The last temptation (Disc two), 2002; SR-16068; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16067. Double album.
          Catalog # 440 063 489-1; A-side Matrix # 440-063-289-1A
        - Ja Rule - Thug lovin', 2002; SR-16069; Ja Rule; Brown, Bobby (Box 303)
          Catalog # DEFR 15717-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15717-1A
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc one), 2001; SR-16070; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16071. Double album.
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc two), 2001; SR-16071; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16070. Double album.
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc one), 2001; SR-16072; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16073. Double album.
        - Ja Rule - Pain is love (Exclusive album advance radio) (Disc two), 2001; SR-16073; Ja Rule (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16072. Double album.
        - Jaam Bros. - Shake it down, 1990; SR-16074; Jaam Bros. (Box 303)
          Catalog # V-71764; A-side Matrix # V-1-71764 F-1
          Life Records
        - Jabara, Paul - Paul Jabara and friends, 1983; SR-16075; Jabara, Paul; Weather Girls; Houston, Whitney (Box 303)
          Catalog # FC-38458; A-side Matrix # P AL 38458-1F
          Columbia
        - Jackal "The Bear" - For real, 1995; SR-16076; Jackal "The Bear" (Box 303)
          Catalog # UR713; A-side Matrix # UR-713-A
          Union Records
          Aston, Pennsylvania
        - Jackal & Hyde - Give it all you got 2000, 2000; SR-16077; Jackal & Hyde (Box 303)
          Catalog # HAL 012; A-side Matrix # HAL-012-A
          Hallucination
          Tampa, Florida
        - Jackal The Bear - For real (Baka Boyz re-mixes), 1996; SR-16078; Jackal The Bear; Baka Boyz (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16079. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WAR-189BB; A-side Matrix # WAR189BB-R-A
          Warlock Records
        - Jackal The Bear - For real (Baka Boyz re-mixes), 1996; SR-16079; Jackal The Bear; Baka Boyz (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16078. 2 copies.
        - Jackers - Down 4 life, 1996; SR-16080; Jackers (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16081. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EAS 7756; A-side Matrix # XSS-7756-A
          Immortal Records
        - Jackers - Down 4 life, 1996; SR-16081; Jackers (Box 303)
          In same jacket as # SR-16080. 2 copies.
        - Jacki-O - Sugar walls, 2004; SR-16082; Jacki-O (Box 303)
          Catalog # 311014; A-side Matrix # 311014-A
          Poe Boy Entertainment
          Miami, Florida
        - Jacki-O - Fine, 2004; SR-16083; Jacki-O; Ying Yang Twins (Box 303)
          Catalog # TV-2664-0; A-side Matrix # TV-2664-0A
          TVT Records
        - Jackie's Gang - Smoke the house, 1987; SR-16084; Jackie's Gang (Box 303)
          Catalog # MSR 2299; A-side Matrix # MSR-1-2299-A
          MSR International
        - J.M. Silk - Let the music take control, 1987; SR-16085; J.M. Silk (Box 303)
          Catalog # 5958-1-RD; A-side Matrix # 5958-1-RDA 1
          RCA
        - J.M. Silk - Music is the key, 1985; SR-16086; J.M. Silk (Box 303)
          Catalog # D.J. 888; A-side Matrix # DJ888AX
          D.J. International Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Jackmate - Recall, 2000; SR-16087; Jackmate (Box 303)
          Catalog # PFR 04; A-side Matrix # PFR 04 A
          Poker Flat Recordings
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Jackson 5 - Diana Ross presents the Jackson 5, 1981; SR-16088; Jackson 5 (Box 303)
          Catalog # M5-129V1; A-side Matrix # M5-129V1-A-158
          Motown
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Jackson 5 - Dancing machine (Remixes), 1992; SR-16089; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          Catalog # 3746310801; A-side Matrix # 37463 1080 1A
          Los Angeles, California
        - Jackson 5 - Soul source Jackson 5 remixes 2 (Disc one), 2001; SR-16090; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          Catalog # UPHJ-1020; A-side Matrix # UPJH-1020A
          Japan
        - Jackson 5 - Anthology (Disc two), 1976; SR-16091; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16092. Double album.
          Catalog # M7-868R3; A-side Matrix # M7-898R3 2603-S-06 A
        - Jackson 5 - Anthology (Disc three), 1976; SR-16092; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16091. Double album.
          Catalog # M7-868R3; A-side Matrix # M7-868R3 2605-S-06 A
        - Jackson 5 - Soul source Jackson 5 remixes 2 (Disc one), 2001; SR-16093; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          Catalog # UPJH-1020; A-side Matrix # UPJH-1020A
        - Jackson 5 - Soul source Jackson 5 remixes 2 (Disc two), 2001; SR-16094; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          Catalog # UPJH-1021; A-side Matrix # UPJH-1021A
        - Jackson 5 - Soul source Jackson 5 remixes 2 (Disc three), 2001; SR-16095; Jackson 5 (Box 304)
          Catalog # UPHJ-1022; A-side Matrix # UPJH-1002A
        - Jackson 5 - I want you back '98, 1998; SR-16096; Jackson 5; Black Rob (Box 304)
          Catalog # 374 633 004-1; A-side Matrix # 374633004-1-A
        - Jacksons - State of shock, 1984; SR-16097; Jacksons (Box 304)
          Catalog # 49 05022; A-side Matrix # XSS-169708-1D
          Epic
        - Jacksons - Victory, 1984; SR-16098; Jacksons (Box 304)
          Catalog # QE 38946; A-side Matrix # PAL 38946-1D
        - Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band - Twas the night before Christmas, 1982; SR-16099; Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band; Little Rodney C (Box 304)
          Catalog # ER-422; A-side Matrix # ER 422-A-12
          Euphoria Records
          United States
        - Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band - Have a happy Christmas (T'was the night before Christmas), 1983; SR-16100; Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band (Box 304)
          Catalog # PT 105; A-side Matrix # PT-105-A
          Partytime Records
        - Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band - Have a happy Christmas (T'was the night before Christmas), 1983; SR-16101; Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band (Box 304)
        - Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band - Have a happy Christmas (T'was the night before Christmas), 1983; SR-16102; Billy Jackson and the Citizen Band (Box 304)
        - Jackson, Chad - Hear the drummer (Get wicked), 1990; SR-16103; Jackson, Chad (Box 304)
          Catalog # 0-96447; A-side Matrix # STDM-59069-1
          ATCO Records
        - Jackson, Charles - I'm gonna get your love, 1979; SR-16104; Jackson, Charles (Box 304)
          Catalog # SPRO-9218; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9218(95909A)-G1
          Capitol Records
        - Jackson, Ronald - Cinderella (Queen of the dance); Hymn for Africa, 1977; SR-16105; Jackson, Ronald; Daniel Jackson Explosion; Besquet, D.B. (Box 304)
          Catalog # S-12454; A-side Matrix # S-3303-LA
          Sam Records
          Long Island City, New York
        - Jackson, Freddie - I don't want to lose your love, 1987; SR-16106; Jackson, Freddie (Box 304)
          Catalog # V-15279; A-side Matrix # V-1-15279-100 492 A
        - Jackson, Freddie - Look around, 1986; SR-16107; Jackson, Freddie (Box 304)
          Catalog # V-15336; A-side Matrix # V-1-15336-100 488/488 A
        - Jackson, Freddie - Nice 'n' slow, 1988; SR-16108; Jackson, Freddie (Box 304)
          Catalog # V-15383; A-side Matrix # V-1-15383-Z1-DMM
        - Jackson, Freddie - He'll never love you (like I do), 1985; SR-16109; Jackson, Freddie (Box 304)
          Catalog # V-15213; A-side Matrix # V-1-15213-99752 B-Z1
        - Jackson, Freddie - You are my lady, 1985; SR-16110; Jackson, Freddie (Box 304)
          Catalog # V-8650; A-side Matrix # V-1-8650-99755-Z1
        - Jackson, Ike - Dollar bill; This is how we do; I know what you want, 2001; SR-16111; Jackson, Ike; U.N.I. (Box 304)
          Catalog # 88561-1998-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1998-1 A
          Loud Records
        - Jackson, Janet - Miss you much, 1989; SR-16112; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12315; A-side Matrix # A+M-012315-A RE 1 ES 2
          A&M Records
        - Jackson, Janet - Come give your love to me, 1982; SR-16113; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-17217; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-017217-A
        - Jackson, Janet - Control, 1986; SR-16114; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12209; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012209-A ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - All for you, 2001; SR-16115; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # VSTX 1801; A-side Matrix # VST-X-1801-A1
          Virgin
          London, United Kingdom
        - Jackson, Janet - Control - the remixes, 1987; SR-16116; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # MIXLP 1; A-side Matrix # MIXLP1 A11
        - Jackson, Janet - Any time, any place, 1993; SR-16117; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # Y-38435; A-side Matrix # Y-38435-A
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Jackson, Janet - Go deep (Disc one), 1998; SR-16118; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16119. Double album.
          Catalog # VSTDJ 1680; A-side Matrix # VSTDJ 1680 A-01-1-
        - Jackson, Janet - Go deep (Disc two), 1998; SR-16119; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16118. Double album.
          Catalog # VSTDJ 1680; A-side Matrix # VSTDJ 1680 C-01-1-
        - Jackson, Janet - Alright, 1990; SR-16120; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # USAT 693; A-side Matrix # USAT 693 A-1U-1-1
        - Jackson, Janet - All for you (Disc one), 2001; SR-16121; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16122. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 10144 1 7; A-side Matrix # V1-7243-8-10144-1-7-A
        - Jackson, Janet - All for you (Disc two), 2001; SR-16122; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16121. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 10144 1 7; A-side Matrix # V1 7243-8-10144-1-7-C
        - Jackson, Janet - What have you done for me lately, 1986; SR-16123; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12167; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012167-A ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - Say you do, 1982; SR-16124; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12059; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012059-A ES1
          Santa Monica, California
        - Jackson, Janet - Nasty, 1986; SR-16125; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16126. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12178; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012178-A ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - Nasty, 1986; SR-16126; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16125. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12196; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012196A ES2
        - Jackson, Janet - Don't stand another chance, 1984; SR-16127; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12105; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012105-B ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - Control (Video mix: soundtrack to the video of control), 1986; SR-16128; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12218; A-side Matrix # SPO-12218-A
        - Jackson, Janet - When I think of you (Dance remix), 1986; SR-16129; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SP-12193; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012193-A ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - All for you, 2001; SR-16130; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          Catalog # SPRO-16155; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-49488-1-7 A
        - Jackson, Janet - Someone to call my lover (Disc one), 2001; SR-16131; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16132. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO-16404; A-side Matrix # SPRO-16404-A
        - Jackson, Janet - Someone to call my lover (Disc two), 2001; SR-16132; Jackson, Janet (Box 304)
          In same jacket as # SR-16131. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO-16404; A-side Matrix # SPRO-16404-C
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Jermaine Jackson, 1984; SR-16133; Jackson, Jermaine (Box 304)
          Catalog # AL 8-8203; A-side Matrix # AL8-8203-SA-9
          Arista
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Do you remember me?, 1986; SR-16134; Jackson, Jermaine (Box 304)
          Catalog # ADI-9501; A-side Matrix # AD1 9501 SA-ES1
        - Jackson, Jesse - Our time has come, 1984; SR-16135; Jackson, Jesse (Box 304)
          Catalog # MCA-5530; A-side Matrix # MCA-4192-AR2
          Constellation Records
          Universal City, California
        - Jackson, Jimmy - Freedom to express yourself, 1979; SR-16136; Jackson, Jimmy (Box 304)
          Catalog # DSC 136; A-side Matrix # DSC-136A-1C
          Buddah Records
        - Jackson, La Toya - Heart don't lie, 1984; SR-16137; Jackson, La Toya (Box 304)
          Catalog # BFZ 39361; A-side Matrix # PAL 39361-1B
          Private I Records
        - Jackson, La Toya - Imagination, 1986; SR-16138; Jackson, La Toya (Box 304)
          Catalog # 4Z9-05389; A-side Matrix # P (AP) 4Z9-05389-3AE
          CBS Associated Records
        - Jackson, La Toya - Such a wicked love, 1988; SR-16139; Jackson, La Toya (Box 304)
          Catalog # 8874-1-RDCD; A-side Matrix # 8874-1-RDCD-C-1
        - Jackson, La Toya - Stay the night, 1981; SR-16140; Jackson, La Toya (Box 304)
          Catalog # PDD-518 DJ; A-side Matrix # POD-518-81NP-5619-PRC-C1-1-1
          Polydor
        - Jackson, Leon - The dancin' lamb, 1983; SR-16141; Jackson, Leon (Box 304)
          Catalog # SRR-1002; A-side Matrix # 13550-A
          Still Rising Records
        - Jackson, Mahalia - Silent night-songs for Christmas, 1962; SR-16142; Jackson, Mahalia (Box 305)